## Rahul Yadav

+91 9987456648

ydvrahul8@gmail.com | www.github.com/ydvrahul8 | www.linkedin.com/in/ydvrahul8/

## **ABOUT ME**

I have been developing Android apps since 2015, and I have developed many applications and published on Google Play Store. I have developed apps like SpotShot, ValueScent, Zolt, MotoMojo.

I also develop iOS apps using flutter. It's been a year since I started working on flutter.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **E|Matrix |** Sr. Android Developer **Dec 2019 - Present |** Mumbai

- Worked as Sr. Android Developer and Project Manager on more than 10 projects with the total team member of 10 people.
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=c om.fh.payday&hl=en\_IN
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=c om.dpoint.dpointsuser
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=c om.dpoints.dpointsmerchant

## Vapa Tech | Sr. Android Developer Oct 2018 - Nov 2019 | Mumbai

- Worked as Sr. Android Developer and Product Lead on 2 projects with the total team member of 3 people.
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=c om.newsapp.admobs&hl=en\_IN
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=c om.valuecent.vapa.incent&hl=en\_IN

### Motomojo | Sr. Android Developer Apr 2016 - Oct 2018 | Mumbai

- Worked as Sr. Android Developer on 2 projects with the total team member of 3 people.
- Motomojo was a startup and over there I helped to design the UI/Ux and build the apps.

## **Concerto Software** Jr. Android Developer **Apr 2015 - Apr 2016** | Navi Mumbai

• Worked as Jr. Android Developer on 3 projects with the total team member of 2 people.

## **SKILLS**

#### **Technical Skills**

Proficient with:

Android | Java | Kotlin | MVVM | GIT | Firebase | UI/UX | Retrofit

Familiar with:

Flutter | Dart | RxDart | Block Pattern | Dagger2

#### Soft Skills

Leadership | Problem Solving | Decision Making | Creative

## **EDUCATION**

# Vivekanand Education Society Institute of Technology (VESIT)

Master of Computer Applications
University Of Mumbai | Graduated 2020

• CGPA - 7.5

## Vidyalankar School of Information Technology (VSIT)

BSc IT

University Of Mumbai | Graduated 2014

• Percentage - 75%

### **Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC/12th)**

University Of Mumbai | Passed 2011

• Percentage - 60.5%

#### Secondary School Certificate (SSC/10th)

University Of Mumbai | Passed 2011

• Percentage - 75.23%

## **FUN FACTS**

#### Interests

Mobile | Gadgets

#### **Hobbies**

Playing Cricket | Listing Music | Movies